1

Privacy Statement

Last Updated: December 18, 2019Kyocera is committed to protecting your privacy. Accordingly, this Privacy Statement isdesigned to help you better understand how we collect, use, store, process, and transferyour Personal Information when using our web sites and/or services (collectively, “Services”).

Consent

Please carefully review this Privacy Statement, its related Notices and our Terms of Use.Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Statement, terms used in this Privacy Statementhave the same meanings as terms defined in our Terms of Use. By using our Services, youacknowledge and consent to all of the policies, procedures and terms described in theforegoing documents. If you do not agree with or you are not comfortable with any aspect ofthis Privacy Statement, the Notices or our Terms of Use, you should immediately discontinueuse of our Services.

Contents

1. Information We Collecta. Information you provide directly to usb. Information related to our Servicesc. Other types of information2. How We Use your Informationa. To fulfill our contract with you and to provide you with Servicesb. To provide customer supportc. To provide marketing communications3. Information We Share with Third Partiesa. Information We Share with Related Entitiesb. Information We Share as Required by Lawc. Business Transactions4. Respecting Your Rights Under Data Privacy Laws and Your Choicesa. Utilizing our Contact Formb. Marketing Communicationsc. Account Modification5. Security Measures6. Storage Duration7. Children's Privacy8. Linked Websites9. Changes to this Privacy Statement10. Contact Information

Information We Collect

We collect the following Personal Information you provide directly to us:

Personal Information you provide when using our Services or creating a Kyocera account:

• Data that identifies you, such as your name, address, telephone numbers or emailaddresses, or your user name provided when setting up your Kyocera account or at alater date.

• Financial information (e.g. credit card and account numbers, payment details) inconnection with a transaction.

2

• Shipping, billing, and other information you provide in connection with the purchaseor shipping of an item, as well as information required for customs clearance (suchas tax identification numbers or other identification numbers) and relevant shippinginformation (such as shipment numbers and tracking information) if shipped throughone of our programs.

• Information provided through a web form or by updating or adding information to yourKyocera account, by participating in product inquiries, dispute resolution, customerservice calls recorded with your consent, or through other contact with us for anyother reason regarding Services.

• Other data we are required or entitled by applicable law to collect and process andneeded for your authentication or identification, or for the verification of the data wecollect.

We collect the following Personal Information related to our Services:

Personal Information we collect automatically when you use our Services or create a

Kyocera account

• Data generated as part of one of your transactions or that is linked to your Kyoceraaccount as a result of a transaction in which you are involved, such as transactionamounts, time and location of transactions and payment methods.

• Data generated through your other actions when you use our Services and which islinked to your Kyocera account, e.g., when you place items in your shopping cart,place items on a watch list, or save searches or interests.

• Data regarding all other interactions with our Services, your advertising preferences,and your communications with us.

• Location data, including the location data of your mobile device. Please note that formost mobile devices, you can manage or disable the use of location services for allapplications in the settings menu of your mobile device.

• Computer and connection information, such as statistics regarding your use ofServices, information on data traffic to and from websites, referral URL, informationon advertisements, your IP address, your access times, your browser history data,your language settings and your weblog information.Personal Information we collect in connection with the use of cookies and similar

technologies

• We use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to collect data while you useour Services. We collect this data from the devices (including mobile devices) usedby you to access our Services. The data collected includes the following usage- anddevice-related information:

o Data about the pages you visit, the access time, frequency and duration ofvisits, the links on which you click and other actions you take as part of youruse of our Services and in advertising and email content.

o Data about your activities and interactions with our advertising partnersincluding data about the advertisements you were shown, how often theywere shown, when and where they were shown, and whether you took anyaction, such as clicking on an advertisement or making a purchase.

• Your user segment.

• Model or device type, operating system and version, browser type and settings,device ID or individual device identifier, advertisement ID, individual device token,and cookie-related data (e.g. cookie ID).

3

• The IP address from which your device accesses the Services.

• Location data, possibly including the location data of your mobile device. Please notethat most mobile devices allow you to manage or disable the use of location servicesfor all applications in the settings menu.

More Information on Cookies. When you use our Services, we and selected thirdparties may use cookies and similar technologies to provide you with a better, faster andsafer user experience or to show you personalized advertising. Cookies are small textfiles that are automatically created by your browser and stored on your device when youuse the Services.

Google Analytics. Google Analytics is used to perform some of the tasks listed above.We do not merge information collected through any Google advertising product withindividual-level information collected elsewhere by our Service. Learn more about howGoogle collects and uses data here. To opt out of Google Analytics Advertising Features

please use Google Ad Settings. To opt out of Google Analytics entirely please use this

link.

We collect other types of information:

• We continuously work to enhance our Services with new products, applicationsand features that may result in the collection of new and different types ofinformation. We will update this Privacy Statement and the Notices and/or obtainyour prior consent to new processing, as needed.

How We Use Your Information

We use your Personal Information for various purposes and pursuant to various legalauthorizations. We use your Personal Information primarily to provide and improve ourServices, to provide you with a personalized user experience on this website, to contact youabout your Kyocera account and our Services, to provide customer service, to provide youwith personalized advertising and marketing communications, and to detect, prevent,mitigate and investigate fraudulent or illegal activity. Kyocera does not sell, lease, or rentyour individual-level Personal Information to third parties and will not do so withoutyour consent.

We may use your Personal Information for the following purposes:

To fulfill our contract with you and to provide you with our Services, including:

• Opening your account, to enable purchases and process payments, tocommunicate with you, and to implement your requests (e.g., referrals).

• Enabling and enhancing your use of our website and mobile application(s),including authenticating your visits, providing personalized content andinformation, and tracking your usage of our Services.

• Contacting you about your account, and any relevant information about ourServices (e.g. policy changes, security updates or issues, etc.).

• Monitoring, detecting, investigating and preventing prohibited or illegal behaviorsrelated to our Services and to combat spam and other security risks.

• Performing research and development activities, which may include, for example,conducting data analysis in order to develop new or improve existing productsand services, and performing quality control activities.

• Enabling the delivery of purchased items by logistics/shipping service providersincluding notifications in connection with the delivery (such as tracking

4

information), the latter to the extent permitted by applicable law without yourconsent.

• Providing payment services.

• Resolving problems with your Kyocera account, arbitrating disputes, providingother services within the scope of customer service, and enforcing fee claims.

• Processing of general location data (such as IP address or postal code) in orderto provide you with location-based services (such as radius search and othercontent that is personalized on the basis of your general location data).

• Enforcing this Privacy Statement, the Notices, and/or the Terms of Use and/orany other applicable policies, procedures and rules.

• For identifying all Personal Information and using the remaining data for historical,statistical and scientific purposes.

Where necessary, we transmit your Personal Information to processors and the followingrecipients for one or several of the purposes described above:

• External service providers and shipping companies.

• Payment service providers.

• External operators of websites, applications, services and tools.

To provide customer support, including:

• Answering your questions, resolving disputes, and/or investigating andtroubleshooting problems or complaints.

• Analyzing telephone conversations with our customer service that we recorded withyour consent.

Where necessary, we transmit your Personal Information to processors and the followingrecipients for one or several of the purposes described above:

• External operators of websites, applications, services and tools.

To provide marketing communications, including:

• Sending you product and promotional emails or notifications about our Services andoffers on new products, services, promotions or contests.

• Evaluating the quality and success of our email marketing campaigns (e.g. throughanalysis of click rates).You can unsubscribe from receiving these marketing communications at any time. Tounsubscribe, follow the directions provided in your online Kyocera account. To opt-out ofreceiving website and mobile notifications, you may do so within your browser or devicesettings. Please note, the opt-out process differs between web browsers and mobile devices.You may not opt-out of receiving non-promotional messages regarding your Kyoceraaccount, such as technical notices, purchase confirmations, or Service-related emails.

Where necessary, we transmit your Personal Information to processors and the followingrecipients for one or several of the purposes described above:

• External operators of websites, applications, services and tools

Information We Share with Third Parties

While Kyocera directly conducts the majority of data processing activities required to provideServices to you, we engage some third party service providers. Service providers are third

5

parties (other companies or individuals) that help us to provide, analyze and improveServices.When Kyocera does share Personal Information, it will require third party service providersto use the Personal Information in a manner consistent with the purposes for which it wasoriginally collected (or to which you subsequently consented) and only as permitted underthis Privacy Statement, the Notices and Terms of Use, and any applicable country or website privacy statements, and all applicable privacy and data protection laws. These thirdparties are required to use the Personal Information Kyocera shares with them only toperform services on Kyocera's behalf and to treat your Personal Information as confidential.In certain, limited circumstances Kyocera may share or transfer Personal Information tounrelated third parties. For example, we may provide Personal Information to a third party: (i)at your request; (ii) to comply with a legal requirement or court order; (iii) to investigate apossible crime, such as identity theft; (iv) in connection with the sale, purchase, merger,reorganization, liquidation or dissolution of Kyocera or a Kyocera business unit; or (v) undersimilar circumstances. If any such event occurs, Kyocera will take appropriate steps toprotect your Personal Information.Specific examples of third party service provider engagement include:

Order Fulfilment and Shipping:

• Our payment processor processes certain Personal Information, such as your billingaddress and credit card information, as necessary to enable your purchase ourproducts.

• Our distribution centers ship our products to you and assist in the return of products ifnecessary.

Customer Service:

• Our customer service department uses a number of tools to organize and managethe requests we receive, most of which are hosted by third party platforms (e.g.customer relationship management software).

Cloud Storage, IT and Security:

• Our cloud storage providers provide secure storage for information in Kyoceradatabases, ensure our infrastructure can support continued use of our Services byKyocera customers, and protect data in the event of a natural disaster or otherdisruption to our Service. Our IT and security service providers assist with intrusiondetection and prevention measures to stop any potential attacks against ournetworks.Information We Share with Other Kyocera Related Entities

We may share some or all of your Personal Information with other companies undercommon ownership or control of Kyocera which may include our subsidiaries, our corporateparent, and other affiliates in order to provide you better service and improve your userexperience. When we do so, these other Kyocera related companies will use your PersonalInformation in a manner consistent with the purposes for which it was originally collected (orto which you subsequently consented) and only as permitted under this Privacy Statement,the Notices, the Terms of Use, any applicable country or web site privacy statements, and allapplicable privacy and data protection laws.

6

Information We Share as Required by Law

Under certain circumstances your Personal Information may be subject to processingpursuant to laws, regulations, judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders.For example, we may be required to disclose Personal Information in coordination withregulatory authorities in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meetnational security or law enforcement requirements. Kyocera will preserve and disclose anyand all Personal Information to law enforcement agencies or others if required to do so bylaw or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessaryto: (a) comply with legal or regulatory process (such as a judicial proceeding, court order, orgovernment inquiry) or obligations that Kyocera may owe pursuant to ethical and otherprofessional rules, laws, and regulations; (b) enforce the Kyocera Terms of Use and otherpolicies; (c) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; or (d)protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Kyocera, its employees, its users, its clients,and the public.Business Transactions

In the event that Kyocera goes through a business transition such as a merger, acquisitionby another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information willlikely be among the assets transferred. In such a case, your Personal Information wouldremain subject to the terms contained in this or any other prior Privacy Statement, Noticesand Terms of Use.

Respecting Your Rights Under Data Privacy Laws and Your Choices

Kyocera is fully committed to performing its obligations and respecting your rights under allapplicable data privacy laws. In this regard, if you reside or otherwise find yourself in ajurisdiction with unique data privacy laws, Kyocera is committed to respecting your rightsgranted by such laws.

Utilizing Our Contact Form

If you have questions about your privacy rights, or would like to exercise your rights underapplicable data privacy laws, please do so via our online contact form available at

https://contact.kyocera.co.jp/inquiry/us/ccpa/input.html. If you prefer, you can send us

correspondence to: Kyocera International, Inc., 8611 Balboa Avenue, San Diego, CA, 92123USA, Attn: Webmaster / Privacy Policy. Alternatively, you can call our toll-free number at(844) 991-1004.Kyocera is obligated to verify the identity of anyone to whom we release PersonalInformation to ensure that Personal Information is released to only authorized parties. Insome cases, you may be required to provide a separate Proof of Identity (“POI”) and Proof ofAddress (“POA”) for us to process your request. Any POI or POA you provide in connectionwith your request will be used solely for the purpose of identity verification related to yourrequest. We may retain such POI/POA Personal Information as part of our record keepingfor this transaction only, and any such Personal Information is covered by our normal dataprotection policies and practices.Marketing Communications

As noted previously, you may be asked to opt-in to receive product and promotional emailsor notifications when creating your Kyocera account or when using our Services. You mayview or update your notification preferences for marketing communications by visiting yourKyocera account, opting out at the browser or device level, or by contacting us using our

7

contact form available at https://contact.kyocera.co.jp/inquiry/us/ccpa/input.html. You can

also click the "unsubscribe" button at the bottom of promotional email communications, asapplicable. For technical reasons, the implementation may take a few days.Account Modification

You may edit, access, correct or update most of your Personal Information on your ownwithin your Kyocera account by following the directions contained in your account.

Security Measures

Your Personal Information will generally be stored in Kyocera databases or databasesmaintained by our service providers. Most of these databases are stored on servers locatedin the United States. To the extent required by law, if your Personal Information will betransferred outside your country, any required notice will be provided.Kyocera maintains reasonable safeguards to protect the confidentiality, security and integrityof your Personal Information. Although Kyocera uses security measures to help protect yourPersonal Information against unauthorized disclosure, misuse or alteration, as is the casewith all computer networks linked to the Internet, Kyocera cannot guarantee the security ofinformation provided over the Internet and will not be responsible for breaches of securitybeyond its reasonable control.

Your Responsibility

Please recognize that protecting your Personal Information is also your responsibility. Weask you to be responsible for safeguarding your password for your Kyocera account, andother authentication information you use to access our Services. You should not discloseyour authentication information to any third party and should immediately notify Kyocera ofany unauthorized use of your password.

Storage Duration

Your Personal Information will be stored by us and our service providers in accordance withapplicable data protection laws to the extent necessary for the processing purposes set outin this Privacy Statement, the Notices and Terms of Use.Subsequently, we will delete your Personal Information in accordance with our data retentionand deletion policy or take steps to properly render the data anonymous, unless we arelegally obliged to keep your Personal Information longer (e.g. for tax, accounting or auditingpurposes).

Children’s Privacy

Kyocera is committed to protecting the privacy of children as well as adults. Neither Kyoceranor any of its Services are designed for, intended to attract, or directed toward childrenunder the age of 16. Kyocera does not knowingly solicit or collect Personal Information fromor about children on its Internet sites.If your child has submitted Personal Information and you would like to request that suchinformation be deleted from Kyocera's records, you may do so using our contact formavailable at https://contact.kyocera.co.jp/inquiry/us/ccpa/input.html. If you prefer, you can

send us correspondence to: Kyocera International, Inc., 8611 Balboa Avenue, San Diego,CA, 92123 USA, Attn: Webmaster / Privacy Policy. Alternatively, you can call our toll-freenumber at (844) 991-1004.

8

Linked Websites

Kyocera provides links to third party websites operated by organizations not affiliated withKyocera. Except as provided above, Kyocera does not disclose your Personal Information toorganizations operating such linked third party websites. Kyocera does not review orendorse and is not responsible for the privacy practices of these organizations. Weencourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that you visit. ThisPrivacy Statement, the Notices and our Terms of Use apply solely to information collected byKyocera and our service providers on our behalf.

Changes to the Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Statement, the Notices and our Terms of Use atour discretion and at any time. When we make changes to this Privacy Statement, we willindicate on our web site that the Privacy Statement, the Notices and/or Terms of Use havebeen updated. Your continued use of the Kyocera web site following the posting of changesconstitutes your acceptance of such changes.By continuing to access or use the Services after changes to this Privacy Statement, theNotices and/or the Terms of Use become effective, you agree to be bound by the revisedPrivacy Statement, Notices and/or Terms of Use. If any changes are unacceptable to you,you may stop using our Services and delete your account at any time.We also may provide additional "just-in-time" disclosures or additional information about thePersonal Information collection, use and sharing practices of specific Services. Such noticesmay supplement or clarify our privacy practices or may provide you with additional choicesabout how Kyocera processes your Personal Information.

Contact Information

If you have questions about this Privacy Statement, the Notices or Terms of Use, or wish tosubmit a complaint, request or inquiry, you may do so using our contact form available at

https://contact.kyocera.co.jp/inquiry/us/ccpa/input.html If you prefer, you can send us

correspondence to: Kyocera International, Inc., 8611 Balboa Avenue, San Diego, CA, 92123USA, Attn: Webmaster / Privacy Policy. Alternatively, you can call our toll-free number at(844) 991-1004.
